A Guide to the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial records FA061
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1917-1949; 3
  - Appropriations - Child Study and Parent Education, 3_05
    - Child Study Fellowships - Cleveland Foundation, 1929-1931 (Box 29, Folder 308)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Committee on Child Development, 1929-1931 (Box 29, Folder 309)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Los Angeles, 1925-1929 (Box 29, Folder 310)
      Problem children - W. I. Thomas, Miriam Van Waters.
    - Child Study Fellowships - National Council of Parent Education, 1928-1931 (Box 29, Folder 311)
    - Child Study Fellowships - National Council of Parent Education, 1928-1931 (Box 29, Folder 312)
    - Child Study Fellowships - National Council of Parent Education, 1928-1931 (Box 29, Folder 313)
    - Child Study Fellowships - Regents of the University of the State of New York, 1929-1931 (Box 29, Folder 314)
    - Child Study Policy, 1923-1929 (Box 30, Folder 315)
    - Child Study Policy, 1923-1929 (Box 30, Folder 316)
    - Cleveland Foundation, 1925-1931 (Box 30, Folder 317)
      LSRM-SF. Parent Education experiment through Cleveland Board of Education; center.
    - Cleveland Foundation, 1925-1931 (Box 30, Folder 318)
    - Cleveland Foundation, 1925-1931 (Box 30, Folder 319)
    - Committee on Child Development, 1924-1930 (Box 30, Folder 320)
      LSRM-SF. National Research Council, research, general background information, fellowships.
    - Committee on Child Development, 1924-1930 (Box 30, Folder 321)
    - Committee on Child Development, 1924-1930 (Box 30, Folder 322)
    - Committee on Child Development, 1924-1930 (Box 30, Folder 323)
    - Committee on Child Development - Scholars (A-D) (Box 31, Folder 324)
    - Committee on Child Development - Scholars (E-M) (Box 31, Folder 325)
    - Committee on Child Development - Scholars (N-R) (Box 31, Folder 326)
    - Committee on Child Development - Scholars (S-Z) (Box 31, Folder 327)
    - Committee on Child Development - Reports (Box 31, Folder 328)
    - Committee on Review, 1924-1949 (Box 31, Folder 329)
    - Conference on Nursery Schools, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 330)
    - Cornell University - Child and Parent Education, 1929-1935 (Box 31, Folder 331)
      SF. Nursery school and extension work, Department of Family Life.
    - Cornell University - Child Training and Extension, 1924-1930 (Box 31, Folder 332)
      LSRM-SF, with Department of Rural Sociology, Resident Work; nursery school, consultation centers, parent study clubs, surveys; extension institute.
    - Cornell University - Child Training and Extension, 1924-1930 (Box 31, Folder 333)
    - Cornell University - Rural Sociology Fellowships, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 334)
    - Council of Parent Education, 1927-1931 (Box 31, Folder 335)
      LSRM-SF. Fellowships.
    - Detroit Board of Education - Parent Education, 1930-1936 (Box 32, Folder 336)
      SF. Parent discussion groups.
    - Detroit Board of Education - Parent Education, 1930-1936 (Box 32, Folder 337)
    - Detroit Board of Education - Parent Education - Reports (Box 32, Folder 338)
    - Home and School Council Fellowships, 1929-1931 (Box 32, Folder 339)
      SF. English fellows in United States.
    - Institut Jean Jacques Rousseau, 1925-1934 (Box 32, Folder 340)
      LSRM-SF. General background information, research center, experimental pedagogy, international bureau on education.
    - Iowa State College of Agriculture, 1925-1931 (Box 32, Folder 341)
      LSRM-SF. Child care laboratory, field work, institutes, demonstrations.
    - Iowa State Teacher's College, 1925-1935 (Box 32, Folder 342)
      LSRM-SF. Resident Child Study program and field workers for extension.
    - McGill University, 1924-1934 (Box 32, Folder 343)
      LSRM-SF. Nursery school, public health nurses and social workers.
    - McGill University, 1924-1934 (Box 32, Folder 344)
    - McGill University, 1924-1934 (Box 32, Folder 345)
    - McGill University - Pamphlets (Box 32, Folder 346)
    - Melony, Mrs. W. B., 1924-1926 (Box 33, Folder 347)
    - Merrill-Palmer School, 1923-1930 (Box 33, Folder 348)
      LSRM-SF. Parent training of college girls, fellowships, conferences, Edna White.
    - Merrill-Palmer School, 1923-1930 (Box 33, Folder 349)
    - Merrill-Palmer School, 1923-1930 (Box 33, Folder 350)
    - Merrill-Palmer School - Conference on Parent Education, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 351)
    - Merrill-Palmer School - Conference on Parent Education, 1926 (Box 33, Folder 352)
    - Merrill-Palmer School - Conference on Homemaking, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 353)
    - Merrill-Palmer School - Reports (Box 33, Folder 354)
    - Mills College, 1926-1934 (Box 33, Folder 355)
      LSRM-SF. Child research center, nursery school and preschool lab; psychology.
    - Mills College, 1926-1934 (Box 33, Folder 356)
    - Mills College, 1926-1934 (Box 33, Folder 357)
    - Monmouth County Organization, 1921-1931 (Box 34, Folder 358)
      LSRM-SF. Demonstration of mobile hygienic clinics, child guidance, problem children in rural schools.
    - Monmouth County Organization, 1921-1931 (Box 34, Folder 359)
    - Monmouth County Organization, 1921-1931 (Box 34, Folder 360)
    - Monmouth County Organization, 1921-1931 (Box 34, Folder 361)
    - Monmouth County Organization, 1921-1931 (Box 34, Folder 362)
    - Monmouth County Organization, 1921-1931 (Box 34, Folder 363)
    - Monmouth County Organization - Reports (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - Monmouth County Organization - Reports (Box 34, Folder 365)
    - Monmouth County Organization - Reports (Box 34, Folder 366)
    - National Child Welfare Association, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 367)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1923-1928 (Box 35, Folder 368)
    - National Council of Parent Education, 1929-1938 (Box 35, Folder 369)
      LSRM-SF. Family and Parent Education, subgroup of White House Conference through National Council of Parent Education (NCPE) for research professor; general background information.
    - National Council of Parent Education, 1929-1938 (Box 35, Folder 370)
    - National Council of Parent Education, 1929-1938 (Box 35, Folder 371)
    - National Council of Parent Education, 1929-1938 (Box 35, Folder 372)
    - National Council of Parent Education - Reports (Box 35, Folder 373)
    - National Council of Parent Education - Fellowships, 1930-1935 (Box 35, Folder 374)
    - National Council of Parent Education - National Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1929-1935 (Box 35, Folder 375)
      SF. General background information, field service to state and local public school administration.
    - National Federation of Day Nurseries, 1926 (Box 35, Folder 376)
    - National Research Council - Committee on Child Development, 1929-1933 (Box 36, Folder 377)
      SF. Conferences, fellowships, abstract and bibliography, clearinghouse.
    - National Research Council - Conference on Child Development, 1925-1933 (Box 36, Folder 378)
      LSRM-SF. Deaf, experimental psychology, racial differences.
    - National Research Council - Conference on Child Development, 1925-1933 (Box 36, Folder 379)
    - National Research Council - Conference on Child Development - Reports (Box 36, Folder 380)
    - National Research Council - Conference on Child Development - Reports (Box 36, Folder 381)
    - National Research Council - Conference on Child Development - Reports (Box 36, Folder 382)
    - National Society for the Study of Education, 1927-1929 (Box 36, Folder 383)
      LSRM-SF. Commission on preschool and parent education.
    - New Orleans Nursery School, 1927-1929 (Box 36, Folder 384)
    - "New Republic", 1926 (Box 36, Folder 385)
    - New York State College for Teachers, 1924-1927 (Box 36, Folder 386)
    - New York State Conference of Parents and Teachers, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 387)
    - North Carolina State Council on Parent Education, 1928-1929 (Box 37, Folder 388)
    - Parents Council, 1924-1928 (Box 37, Folder 389)
    - Parents Publishing Association, 1924-1940 (Box 37, Folder 390)
      LSRM-SF. Magazine "Children" - Yale, Teachers College of Columbia, State University of Iowa, University of Minnesota.
    - Parents Publishing Association, 1924-1940 (Box 37, Folder 391)
    - Parents Publishing Association, 1924-1940 (Box 37, Folder 392)
    - Parents Publishing Association, 1924-1940 (Box 37, Folder 393)
    - Parents Publishing Association, 1924-1940 (Box 37, Folder 394)
    - Parents Publishing Association - Reports (Box 37, Folder 395)
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York., 1926-1936 (Box 38, Folder 396)
      LSRM-SF. Study to establish bureau in state with programs; extend to Albany State Teachers College and Albany Board of Education.
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York., 1926-1936 (Box 38, Folder 397)
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York., 1926-1936 (Box 38, Folder 398)
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York - Reports (Box 38, Folder 399)
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York - Reports (Box 38, Folder 400)
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York - Reports (Box 38, Folder 401)
    - Regents of the University of the State of New York - Reports (Box 38, Folder 402)
    - Rochester Board of Education and the University of Rochester, 1929-1935 (Box 38, Folder 403)
      SF. Nursery School, consultant psychiatrist, demonstration, high school home economics.
    - Rochester Board of Education and the University of Rochester - Reports (Box 39, Folder 404)
    - Ruggles Street Nursery School, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 405)
    - Rural Child Welfare in Virginia, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 406)
    - Rural Sociology, 1925-1928 (Box 39, Folder 407)
      A. R. Mann.
    - St. Cloud State Teachers College, 1927-1935 (Box 39, Folder 408)
      SF. Child Study department, courses, nursery school, parent study group.
    - Selmene Winter Foundation, 1925-1926 (Box 39, Folder 409)
    - Smith College, 1924-1928 (Box 39, Folder 410)
      Institute for coordination of women's interests. Education as wife, mother, intellectual.
    - Smith College, 1924-1928 (Box 39, Folder 411)
    - Smith College - Clippings (Box 39, Folder 412)
    - Smith College - Reports (Box 39, Folder 413)
    - Spelman College, 1930-1937 (Box 39, Folder 414)
      SF. Fund to provide for physical, mental, social, and spiritual well-being of young Negro women in U.S.; nursery school and lab. Florence M. Read.
    - Spelman College, 1930-1937 (Box 39, Folder 415)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 416)
      LSRM-SF. Child Welfare Research Station, home school laboratory, parent training group, demonstration. Bird T. Baldwin.
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 417)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 418)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 419)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 420)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 421)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 422)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 423)
    - State University of Iowa, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 424)
    - State University of Iowa, 1930-1940 (Box 41, Folder 425)
    - State University of Iowa, 1930-1940 (Box 41, Folder 426)
    - State University of Iowa, 1930-1940 (Box 41, Folder 427)
    - State University of Iowa, 1930-1940 (Box 41, Folder 428)
    - State University of Iowa, 1930-1940 (Box 41, Folder 429)
    - State University of Iowa - Parents Publishing Association, 1928-1938 (Box 41, Folder 430)
    - State University of Iowa - Clippings and Pamphlets (Box 41, Folder 431)
    - Swarthmore College, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 432)
    - Teachers College, 1922-1928 (Box 42, Folder 433)
    - Teachers College - Child Research Institute, 1924-1934 (Box 42, Folder 434)
      LSRM-SF. Division of juvenile research and education program, demonstration; training; clearinghouse.
    - Teachers College - Child Research Institute, 1924-1934 (Box 42, Folder 435)
    - Teachers College - Child Research Institute, 1924-1934 (Box 42, Folder 436)
    - Teachers College - Child Research Institute, 1924-1934 (Box 42, Folder 437)
    - Teachers College - Child Research Institute, 1924-1934 (Box 42, Folder 438)
    - Teachers College - Child Research Institute - Reports (Box 42, Folder 439)
    - Teachers College - Child Welfare in Type Community in New York City, 1923-1926 (Box 42, Folder 440)
    - Teachers College - Educational Research, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 441)
    - Teachers College - Fellowships, 1924-1931 (Box 43, Folder 442)
      LSRM-SF. Through Federation for Child Study.
    - Teachers College - Fellowships, 1924-1931 (Box 43, Folder 443)
    - Teachers College - Fellowships, 1924-1931 (Box 43, Folder 444)
    - Teachers College - Fellowships - California, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 445)
    - Teachers College - Parents Publishing Association, 1925-1941 (Box 43, Folder 446)
    - Teachers College - Preschool Child, 1923-1924 (Box 43, Folder 447)
      Nursery.
    - Temple University - Nursery School, 1928-1929 (Box 43, Folder 448)
    - Todd, T. Wingate, 1926-1928 (Box 43, Folder 449)
    - United States Bureau of Education, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 450)
    - United States Department of Labor - Children's Bureau, 1924-1926 (Box 43, Folder 451)
    - University of California, 1923-1934 (Box 43, Folder 452)
      LSRM-SF. Nursery school, home, Institute at Berkeley.
    - University of California, 1923-1934 (Box 43, Folder 453)
    - University of California - Research on Adolescence, 1930-1938 (Box 43, Folder 454)
      SF. Physical and mental growth.
    - University of California - Reports (Box 44, Folder 455)
    - University of Cincinnati - Child Study, 1925-1934 (Box 44, Folder 456)
      LSRM-SF. Nursery school and demonstration center, undergraduate instruction including training of Negros in parent education.
    - University of Cincinnati - Child Study, 1925-1934 (Box 44, Folder 457)
    - University of Georgia College of Agriculture, 1924-1935 (Box 44, Folder 458)
      LSRM-SF. Preschool mother's circles, state wide program; demonstration agents, study groups, courses.
    - University of Georgia College of Agriculture, 1924-1935 (Box 44, Folder 459)
    - University of Georgia College of Agriculture, 1924-1935 (Box 44, Folder 460)
    - University of Georgia College of Agriculture - Reports (Box 44, Folder 461)
    - University of Hamburg - Psychology, 1927-1929 (Box 44, Folder 462)
    - University of Kansas, 1924-1925 (Box 44, Folder 463)
    - University of Michigan, 1925-1929 (Box 44, Folder 464)
    - University of Minnesota, 1921-1944 (Box 45, Folder 465)
      LSRM-RF. Research; child caring, nursery school, parent education; Institute of Child Welfare.
    - University of Minnesota, 1921-1944 (Box 45, Folder 466)
    - University of Minnesota, 1921-1944 (Box 45, Folder 467)
    - University of Minnesota, 1921-1944 (Box 45, Folder 468)
    - University of Minnesota, 1921-1944 (Box 45, Folder 469)
    - University of Minnesota, 1921-1944 (Box 45, Folder 470)
    - University of Minnesota - Reports (Box 45, Folder 471)
    - University of Minnesota - Reports (Box 45, Folder 472)
    - University of Minnesota - Reports (Box 46, Folder 473)
    - University of Minnesota - Reports (Box 46, Folder 474)
    - University of Minnesota - Pamphlets (Box 46, Folder 475)
    - University of Minnesota - Parents Publishing Association, 1928 (Box 46, Folder 476)
    - University of Montana, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 477)
    - University of Nebraska, 1925 (Box 46, Folder 478)
    - University of Toronto - Child Study, 1924-1930 (Box 46, Folder 479)
      LSRM-SF. Interdepartmental nursery school. C. M. Hinks, E. A. Bott.
    - University of Toronto - Child Study, 1924-1930 (Box 46, Folder 480)
    - University of Toronto - Child Study, 1924-1930 (Box 46, Folder 481)
    - University of Toronto - Child Study - Reports (Box 47, Folder 482)
    - Vassar College, 1921-1928 (Box 47, Folder 483)
    - Virginia Day Nursery, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 484)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 485)
    - Wallas, Graham, 1923-1927 (Box 47, Folder 486)
    - Western Reserve University - Conference on Adolescent Research, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 487)
      SF, with Brush Foundation. Child study extension.
    - Western Reserve University - Research in Child Development, 1929-1935 (Box 47, Folder 488)
      SF, with Brush Foundation. Criteria of physiological development. T. Wingate Todd.
    - Western Reserve University - Research in Child Development, 1929-1935 (Box 47, Folder 489)
    - White House Conference on Child Care and Protection, 1929-1930 (Box 47, Folder 490)
    - White House Conference on Child Care and Protection - Proceedings (Box 47, Folder 491)
    - Yale University - Institute of Psychology - Child Research, 1923-1934 (Box 47, Folder 492)
      LSRM-SF. Mental development in preschool child. Arnold Gesell.
    - Yale University - Institute of Psychology - Child Research, 1923-1934 (Box 47, Folder 493)
    - Yale University - Parents Publishing Association, 1927-1928 (Box 47, Folder 494)
  - Appropriations - Social Studies, 3_06
    - Agriculture Survey - Black, 1928-1930 (Box 48, Folder 495)
      LSRM-SF. Agrarian reform.
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1922-1929 (Box 48, Folder 496)
      Research in humanities and social sciences; fellowships. Charles Homer Haskins, Waldo G. Leland, Guy Stanton Ford.
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1922-1929 (Box 48, Folder 497)
    - American Historical Association, 1925-1928 (Box 48, Folder 498)
      International bibliography of the social sciences. Waldo G. Leland.
    - American Institute of Cooperation, 1924-1929 (Box 48, Folder 499)
      Cooperation in economic, legal, and social aspects of study. Clearinghouse.
    - American Law Institute, 1924-1928 (Box 48, Folder 500)
      Model code of criminal procedure. William Draper Lewis, George Wickersham.
    - American Library Association - American Periodicals, 1923-1929 (Box 48, Folder 501)
      To foreign libraries.
    - American Library Association - Foreign Periodicals, 1926-1932 (Box 48, Folder 502)
      LSRM-RF. Union list foreign government serials.
    - American Library Association - League of Nations Library, 1926-1928 (Box 48, Folder 503)
      Cancelled.
    - American Library Association - Union List of Serials, 1923-1928 (Box 48, Folder 504)
    - American Library in Paris, 1927-1930 (Box 48, Folder 505)
    - American Library in Paris - Reference Service, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 506)
      Need of United States and Europe for authentic information.
    - American Library in Paris - Reference Service, 1925-1926 (Box 49, Folder 507)
    - American Psychiatric Association - Conference, 1928 (Box 49, Folder 508)
    - American Psychological Association, 1926-1935 (Box 49, Folder 509)
      LSRM-RF. Psychological Abstracts.
    - American Society of International Law, 1923-1924 (Box 49, Folder 510)
      Subscription to League of Nations Treaty Series.
    - American Statistical Association - Committee on International Statistics, 1928 (Box 49, Folder 511)
      Advisory Committee-LSRM. Conference and report on status of public welfare statistics.
    - American University of Beirut, 1925-1931 (Box 49, Folder 512)
      LSRM-RF. Social science department and commercial education; Fellowships.
    - American University of Beirut, 1925-1931 (Box 49, Folder 513)
    - Balkan Survey - Kerner, 1927-1929 (Box 49, Folder 514)
      LSRM-RF. Social science resources.
    - Balkan Survey - Kerner - Report (Box 49, Folder 515)
    - Bavarian State Library, 1924-1928 (Box 49, Folder 516)
      Social science literature.
    - Brookings Institution, 1923-1931 (Box 49, Folder 517)
      LSRM-RF. Graduate School of Economics and Government. Robert Brookings.
    - Brookings Institution, 1923-1931 (Box 49, Folder 518)
    - Bureau of Public Personnel Information, 1922-1924 (Box 49, Folder 519)
      Advisory Committee. Conference to formulate project-tangible approach for scientific attack on problems; Clearinghouse BPPA under Institute for Government Research. Lewis Meriam.
    - Bureau of Social Hygiene, 1926-1928 (Box 49, Folder 520)
      Leonard V. Harrison. Crime Commission Study; Max Winsor study on Scientific Aspects of Crime.
    - Cambridge University, 1925-1928 (Box 50, Folder 521)
      Chairs of Political Science and Sociology.
    - Cities Census Committee, 1923-1928 (Box 50, Folder 522)
      Additional and interpretive data on New York City. Special publications and general background information.
    - Columbia University - Familial Law, 1928-1929 (Box 50, Folder 523)
      Law in a social setting.
    - Columbia University - Familial Law - Reports (Box 50, Folder 524)
    - Columbia University - Law, 1927-1928 (Box 50, Folder 525)
      Studies: how law affects economic activities, how branches of science bear on criminal law, research in legal education.
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1925-1930 (Box 50, Folder 526)
      LSRM-RF. Mutual cooperation in social science research. Franz Boas.
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, 1925-1930 (Box 50, Folder 527)
    - Columbia University - Social Sciences, French, 1925-1929 (Box 50, Folder 528)
      Contemporary France as a laboratory of social science.
    - Committee in Review - Social Sciences, 1926-1928 (Box 50, Folder 529)
      LSRM Policy.
    - Committee in Review - Social Sciences, 1926-1928 (Box 50, Folder 530)
    - Committee in Review - Social Sciences, 1926-1928 (Box 50, Folder 531)
    - Condliffe, J. B., 1923-1927 (Box 50, Folder 532)
    - Connecticut College - Study of Ethnic Factors, 1928-1930 (Box 51, Folder 533)
      LSRM-RF. In community life. Completing previous study.
    - Connecticut College - Study of Ethnic Factors - Reports (Box 51, Folder 534)
    - Coss, J. J., 1924-1927 (Box 51, Folder 535)
      Special investigation in Far East.
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1927-1928 (Box 51, Folder 536)
      Journal, research.
    - Deutsche Hochschule Fur Politik, 1926-1928 (Box 51, Folder 537)
      General background information, advanced political studies.
    - Economic Foundation, 1922-1928 (Box 51, Folder 538)
      General background information, fact finding among economic, social and industrial phenomena of model community life. Through National Bureau of Economic Resource.
    - Economic Foundation, 1922-1928 (Box 51, Folder 539)
    - Encyclopedia of the Social Sciences, 1926-1928 (Box 51, Folder 540)
    - Fellowship Survey - Lingelbach, 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 541)
    - Fellowship Survey - Lingelbach, 1925-1926 (Box 51, Folder 542)
    - Fellowships - Bilden, 1924-1925 (Box 51, Folder 543)
      Slavery in Brazil.
    - Fellowships - Gleason, 1924-1927 (Box 51, Folder 544)
      Psychopathology.
    - Fellowships - Radin, 1926-1927 (Box 51, Folder 545)
      Indian life - ethnic and linguistics.
    - Fellowships - Thurstone, 1925 (Box 51, Folder 546)
    - Foreign Fellowships - Yellow Sheet (A-H) (Box 51, Folder 547)
    - Foreign Fellowships - Yellow Sheet (I-Z) (Box 52, Folder 548)
    - Foreign Fellowships, 1925-1929 (Box 52, Folder 549)
    - Fisk University, 1926-1930 (Box 52, Folder 550)
      Library, Department of Social Sciences.
    - Flexner, Abraham, 1926-1928 (Box 52, Folder 551)
    - Foreign Language Information Service, 1921-1929 (Box 52, Folder 552)
      Advisory Committee-LSRM. Translate government bulletins to foreign press.
    - Foreign Language Information Service, 1921-1929 (Box 52, Folder 553)
    - Foreign Language Information Service, 1921-1929 (Box 52, Folder 554)
    - Foreign Language Information Service - Manual, 1923-1927 (Box 52, Folder 555)
      A handbook for immigrants.